<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>scene on How artificial intelligence will change the course of Belarus protests 2020</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/scene/</link>
    <description>Recent content in scene on How artificial intelligence will change the course of Belarus protests 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 11:14:48 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/scene/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Facial recognition and Belarus example</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Over last years the facial recognition system is one of the major successes of Artificial intelligence. Facial recognition has always been a field of continuous development and research due to its usage in different areas such as security and robotics. It has gained even more popularity and interest by the researchers with the recent advancements in artificial intelligence and deep learning, which improved the robustness of facial recognition systems. It captures, analyzes, and compares patterns based on the person&amp;rsquo;s facial details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INTRODUCTION</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Every person living in a democratic country knows that their right to make or join a peaceful protest is their right to make or join a peaceful protest if they feel that their rights are not heard by the government, and that they can go to demonstrations without fear from the police or the army, but not every country in the a1st century. History books claim that the Soviet Union no longer exists, but we can be sure that in post-Soviet Union countries such as Ukraine1 and Belarus 2 , its legacy of corruption and policies, army violence, lives on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
